A Guide to the Joseph Francis Fletcher Papers (1931-1991)
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Lectures: course lecture 4 (3 parts), "The Old Testament Background," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 019:032)
- Lectures: course lecture 5 (3 parts), "The Ethical Teachings of Jesus," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 020:001)
- Lectures: course lecture 6 (2 parts), "The Sermon on the Mount," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 020:002)
- Lectures: course lecture 7 (3 parts), "Love as the Norm," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 020:003)
- Lectures: course lecture 8 (2 parts), "John and Paul," "St. Paul's Ethics," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 020:004)
- Lectures: "The Drug Culture: A Confrontation," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:005)
- Lectures: "An End to Conscience," "An End to Ideology," "An End to Human Rights," Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 020:006)
- Lectures: "Humanism and Theism in American Ethics" (draft), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:007)
- Lectures: "On What is Called the New Morality," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:008)
- Lectures: "Refusal of Treatment," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:009)
- Lectures: "The Return of the Sacred" (draft), Joseph Fletcher, with photocopy of book chapter with the same title, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 020:010)
- Lectures: "Science Policy and the Public Interest: A View from the Humanities" (2 drafts), Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 020:011)
- Lectures: untitled, concerning situation ethics and secular humanism (draft), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:012)
- Lectures: drafts and notes for various talks and essays, Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 6 Items (Box-folder 020:013)
- Manuscripts: draft essay on the new morality, by Joseph Fletcher?, [1965] (Box-folder 020:014)
- Manuscripts: "Reversibility Following Sterilization by Vasectomy," Herbert Brewer, [1965] (Box-folder 020:015)
- Manuscripts: "The Exposition of Situation Ethics," J. W. Bluck, 1968 December 16 (Box-folder 020:016)
- Manuscripts: special collection of manuscript drafts, correspondence, notes, and newspaper clippings concerning genetics and medical ethics, 1976-1977, 25 Items (Box-folder 020:017)
- Manuscripts: "Medical Ethics and Anencephaly," Joseph Fletcher, with attached note of Fletcher to [Thomas H. Hunter?], 1988 June 11 (Box-folder 020:018)
- Manuscripts: "Chronic Famine and the Immorality of Food Aid: a Bow to Garrett Hardin," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:019)
- Manuscripts: "Distrust of Philosophers," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:020)
- Manuscripts: "A Document on Fertility Control," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:021)
- Manuscripts: "Ethics and Genetic Control," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:022)
- Manuscripts: "Ethics and Recombinant DNA Research," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:023)
- Manuscripts: "An Exercise in Thinking," Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:024)
- Manuscripts: "Genetics: Shall We Design Our Children?" Joseph Fletcher, N.D. (Box-folder 020:025)
- Manuscripts: "A Pair of Dusty, Battered Wings," Prudence Harvey Hamilton, N.D. (Box-folder 020:026)
- Memoirs: Joseph Fletcher biographical sketch, 1967 (Box-folder 020:027)
- Memoirs: Introduction for Joseph Fletcher, by Dan Maguire, 1978 January 22 (Box-folder 020:028)
- Memoirs: "Memoir of an Ex-Radical," Joseph Fletcher, 1983 July 7 (Box-folder 020:029)
- Memoirs: "Joseph Fletcher: the Father of Biomedical Ethics," Richard Taylor, 1984 Spring (Box-folder 020:030)
- Memoirs: "Recollections" (incomplete copy), Joseph Fletcher, sent to [Thomas H. Hunter], 1984 (Box-folder 020:031)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1950, 1 Item (Box-folder 021:001)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1954, 5 Items (Box-folder 021:002)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1955, 2 Items (Box-folder 021:003)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1956, 6 Items (Box-folder 021:004)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1957, 1 Item (Box-folder 021:005)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1958, 28 Items (Box-folder 021:006)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1959, 31 Items (Box-folder 021:007)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1950s, 50 Items (Box-folder 021:008)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1960, 23 Items (Box-folder 021:009)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1961, 3 Items (Box-folder 021:010)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1963, 7 Items (Box-folder 021:011)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1964, 6 Items (Box-folder 021:012)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1965, 26 Items (Box-folder 021:013)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1966, 46 Items (Box-folder 021:014)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1967, 50 Items (Box-folder 021:015)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1968, 15 Items (Box-folder 021:016)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1969, 45 Items (Box-folder 021:017)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1960s, 48 Items (Box-folder 021:018)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1970s, 10 Items (Box-folder 021:019)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1980s, 92 Items (Box-folder 021:020)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1990s, 5 Items (Box-folder 021:021)
- Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, N.D., 15 Items (Box-folder 021:022)
- Notes: by Joseph Fletcher?, [1965], 1 Item (Box-folder 022:001)
- Notes: on books, [1967], 1 Item (Box-folder 022:002)
- Notes, [1968], 2 Items (Box-folder 022:003)
- Notes: by Joseph Fletcher?, [1960s], 13 Items (Box-folder 022:004)
- Notes: miscellaneous, [1960s], 4 Items (Box-folder 022:005)
- Notes: miscellaneous, [1970s], 59 Items (Box-folder 022:006)
- Notes: for a publication (sections 1, 2, 3), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 71 Items (Box-folder 022:007)
- Notes: for a publication (section 4), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 114 Items (Box-folder 022:008)
- Notes: for a publication (sections 5, 6, 7), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 165 Items (Box-folder 022:009)
- Notes: for a publication (section 8), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 122 Items (Box-folder 022:010)
- Notes: for a publication (section 9), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 143 Items (Box-folder 022:011)
- Notes: for a publication (sections 10, 11, 12), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 156 Items (Box-folder 022:012)
- Notes: for a publication (sections 13, 14, 15, 16, 18, 19), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 90 Items (Box-folder 022:013)
- Notes: for a publication (sections V, VI, VII, VIII, PSI, PSII), Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 30 Items (Box-folder 022:014)
- Notes: unidentified, Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 122 Items (Box-folder 022:015)
- Notes: unidentified, Joseph Fletcher, N.D. [ca. 1970s], 220 Items (Box-folder 023:001)
- Notes: on human psychology, Joseph Fletcher, N.D., 10 Items (Box-folder 023:002)
- Cataloguing error, no folder 3 (Box-folder 023:003)
- Notes: miscellaneous, N.D., 18 Items (Box-folder 023:004)
- Notes: student notes, N.D., 1 Item (Box-folder 023:005)
- Paddock Fund: correspondence and other materials, 1968 October 14-1970 June 20, N.D., 108 Items (Box-folder 023:006)
- Programs-Brochures, 1936-1958, 11 Items (Box-folder 023:007)
- Programs-Brochures, 1960-1964, 32 Items (Box-folder 023:008)
- Programs-Brochures, 1965, 46 Items (Box-folder 023:009)
- Programs-Brochures, 1966, 60 Items (Box-folder 023:010)
- Programs-Brochures, 1967 January-June, 39 Items (Box-folder 024:001)
- Programs-Brochures, 1967 July-December, 46 Items (Box-folder 024:002)
- Programs-Brochures, 1968 January-June, 27 Items (Box-folder 024:003)
- Programs-Brochures, 1968 July-December, 9 Items (Box-folder 024:004)
- Programs-Brochures, 1969 January-June, 34 Items (Box-folder 024:005)
- Programs-Brochures, 1969 July-December, 27 Items (Box-folder 024:006)
- Programs-Brochures, 1960s, 41 Items (Box-folder 024:007)
- Programs-Brochures, 1970s, 7 Items (Box-folder 024:008)
- Programs-Brochures, 1980s-1990s, 5 Items (Box-folder 024:009)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Catholic Social Reform in the Third Republic," 1931 (Box-folder 025:001)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Case Study in Moral Theology," 1934 January (Box-folder 025:002)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Bibliography on 'The Church and Industry'," with S[pencer] M[iller], Jr. 1934 May (Box-folder 025:003)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Money Makers and Moral Man," 1934 August, 2 Items (Box-folder 025:004)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Church and Social Credit," 1934, 2 Items (Box-folder 025:005)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Money Makers and Moral Man," 1934 (Box-folder 025:006)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Was the Early Church Communistic?," with a reprint of the same title by M. K. P. Brannan, [1934], 2 Items (Box-folder 025:007)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christian Doctrine and Social Action," [1935 Autumn], 3 Items (Box-folder 025:008)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Basis of Christian Faith and Action Today," 1937 April, 2 Items (Box-folder 025:009)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Graduate School at the Convention," 1937 September-October (Box-folder 025:010)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "What the Clergy Want to Know about the Community," 1937 (Box-folder 025:011)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Social Training for the Pastoral Ministry," 1940 April (Box-folder 025:012)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Church and Its Community," [1940] (Box-folder 025:013)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Family in the World Today," [1940] (Box-folder 025:014)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "What Should Our Message Be?," 1941 August 21 (Box-folder 025:015)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christian Peace Arms," [1942], 2 Copies (Box-folder 025:016)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Economic Needs of Soldiers," 1944 November 2 (Box-folder 025:017)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Ministry of the Laity," with two notes, 1945 February 1, 3 Items (Box-folder 025:018)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Ministry of the Laity," with two copies of an editorial commenting on Fletcher's essay, 1945 February 1, April, 3 Items (Box-folder 025:019)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Melish Case: Challenge to the Church," [by Joseph Fletcher?, et al], [1947] (Box-folder 025:020)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christianity and Civilization Bibliography," 1948 January, 2 Items (Box-folder 025:021)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Human Nature and Social Action," 1948 April (Box-folder 025:022)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Pastoral Counseling Bibliography," 1948 July (Box-folder 025:023)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christ's Feast or the Devil's," 1949 (Box-folder 025:024)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Euthanasia: Out Right to Die," 1950 April (Box-folder 025:025)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Ethics of Criminal Guilt," 1950 (Box-folder 025:026)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Dr. Fletcher Answers Some Questions," 1951 February (Box-folder 025:027)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Our Right to Die," 1951 July (Box-folder 025:028)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Collectivism: Problem for Christian Ethics," 1951 Autumn (Box-folder 025:029)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Concepts of Moral Responsibility," 1951 October (Box-folder 025:030)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Faith We Live By: the Ministry of the Laity," 1951 December 15 (Box-folder 025:031)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Psychiatry and Religion: Conflict or Synthesis?," 1952 Summer (Box-folder 025:032)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Moral Philosophy of Sex," 1953 February (Box-folder 025:033)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christian Views on Human Labor 1500-1860: from Martin Luther to Samuel Smiles," 1955 March (Box-folder 025:034)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Medical Diagnosis: Our Right to Know the Truth," 1955 April (Box-folder 025:035)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Birth Control: a New Dimension," 1958 Winter (Box-folder 025:036)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Father Huntington: Social Pioneer," 1958 (Box-folder 025:037)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "How Can We Get Enough Clergy," 1959 March 19 (Box-folder 025:038)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Exciting Books: Three of Them," 1959 July (Box-folder 025:039)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "'Love Does Not Insist On Its Own Way' Planned Parenthood and Birth Control," and a later version of the same, 1959 Autumn, 1960 April-June, 2 Items (Box-folder 025:040)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The New Look in Christian Ethics," 1959 October (Box-folder 025:041)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christian Approach to Nuclear War," [1959] (Box-folder 025:042)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Sex Offenses: An Ethical View," 1960 Spring (Box-folder 025:043)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Patient's Right to Die," 1960 October, 2 Items (Box-folder 025:044)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Situational Ethics: A Note for Business Management," 1960 October (Box-folder 025:045)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Dysthanasia: the Problem of Prolonging Death," 1961 December 13 (Box-folder 026:001)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Anti-Dysthanasia: the Problem of Prolonging Death," 1962 February 26, 2 Items (Box-folder 026:002)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Professions: A Theological Fontier," 1962 July (Box-folder 026:003)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Mission to Main Street," 1962 (Box-folder 026:004)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Statement on Business Ethics and a Call for Action," Business Ethics Advisory Council, [1962] (Box-folder 026:005)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Clergyman Speaks on Voluntary Sterilization," [1963 January] (Box-folder 026:006)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The End of the Era of Common Sense," 1963 Spring (Box-folder 026:007)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Moral Tension and an Ethical Frontier," 1963 Autumn (Box-folder 026:008)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christian Ethics in a New Key," [1963] (Box-folder 026:009)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The New Look in Christian Ethics," 1964 June 4 (Box-folder 026:010)
- Reprints, Fletcher: [cataloguing error, no folder 026:011] (Box-folder 026:011)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Love is the Only Measure" (with responses), 1966 January 14 (Box-folder 026:012)
- Reprints, Fletcher: Review of Foreign Policy in Christian Perspective by John C. Bennett, 1966 August 14 (Box-folder 026:013)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "WCC Left-Right Tensions," 1966 August 18 (Box-folder 026:014)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Why New?" [1966?] (Box-folder 026:015)
- Reprints, Fletcher: Review of Toward a Christian Moral Theology by Bernard Haring, 1967 January 22 (Box-folder 026:016)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Issue of Culpability," 1967 August 2-4 (Box-folder 026:017)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Another Note on Situation Ethics," 1967 September (Box-folder 026:018)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Short Response from Joseph Fletcher," 1967 September (Box-folder 026:019)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "About Edmond Cahn," with an invitation to the dedication of the Edmond Cahn Room, New York University Law School, 1967 October 21, 2 Items (Box-folder 026:020)
- Reprints, Fletcher: Letter to U.S. Catholic1967 December (Box-folder 026:021)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Christian Ethics in a New Key," 1967 Winter (Box-folder 026:022)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Love is the Only Measure: a Protestant View," 1967 (Box-folder 026:023)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Tillich and Ethics: the Negation of Law," 1968 February (Box-folder 026:024)
- Reprints, Fletcher: Review of Deeds and Rules in Christian Ethics by Paul Ransey, 1968 March (Box-folder 026:025)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Human Experiments - Some Questions of Ethics," 1968 (Box-folder 026:026)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Right to Die," with Bernard Bard, 1968 April (Box-folder 026:027)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "When Should Patients be Allowed to Die? - Some Questions of Ethics," 1968 April, May (Box-folder 026:028)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Donor Nephrectomies and Moral Responsibility," 1968 December (Box-folder 026:029)
- Reprints, Fletcher: Review of Sexuality and Moral Responsibility by Pobert P. O'Neil and Michael A. Donovan, 1968 (Box-folder 026:030)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Symposium, Jewish Youth and the Sexual Revolution: Joseph Fletcher," 1968-1969 Winter (Box-folder 026:031)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Naturalism, Situation Ethics, and Value Theory," 1969 March (Box-folder 026:032)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "When Does Death Occur?," 1969 April (Box-folder 026:033)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "On Target," 1969 June 18 (Box-folder 026:034)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Is the Best Yet to Be?," 1969 June (Box-folder 026:035)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Broadly Speaking," 1969 November (Box-folder 026:036)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Our Shameful Waste of Human Tissue," 1970 January (Box-folder 026:037)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Virtue is a Predicate," and a revision of the same as: "Goodness," and a mimeograph transcription, 1970 January, N.D., 3 Items (Box-folder 026:038)
- Reprints, Fletcher: Book reviews for The Churchman, 1970 February, N.D., 2 Items (Box-folder 026:039)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Situation Ethics," 1970 March 16-18 (Box-folder 026:040)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Situation Ethics: Progress Report," 1970 March 25 (Box-folder 026:041)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Power," 1970 March (Box-folder 026:042)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethical Aspects of Genetic Controls," 1971 May 14 (Box-folder 026:043)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Prospect for Parsons," 1971 June (Box-folder 026:044)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethical Aspects of Genetic Controls," 1971 September 30 (Box-folder 026:045)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Ethics of Abortion," 1971 December (Box-folder 026:046)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Greatest Good of the Greatest Number," [1971] (Box-folder 026:047)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Promethean Project and Pastoral Care," 1972 April (Box-folder 027:001)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethical Aspects of Genetic Controls" (Appendix B of Congressional Report), with notes and newspaper clippings, 1972 November, 5 Items (Box-folder 027:002)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Marriage: For and Against," 1972 (Box-folder 027:003)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethics and Euthanasia," 1973 April (Box-folder 027:004)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Medicine and the Nature of Man," 1973 (Box-folder 027:004A)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "New Definitions of Death," 1974 January (Box-folder 027:005)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The 'Right' to Live and the 'Right' to Die: a Protestant View of Euthanasia," 1974 July-August (Box-folder 027:006)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Abortion and the True Believer," 1974 November 27 (Box-folder 027:007)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethics and Euthanasia," with "An Alternative to the Ethic of Euthanasia," by Arthur J. Dyck, 2 Items (Box-folder 027:008)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Humanness and Abortion," 1974 (Box-folder 027:009)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Quarter-Century of Christian Ethics at ETS: a Rear View Mirror," [1974?] (Box-folder 027:010)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Situation Ethics and Watergate," 1975 January (Box-folder 027:011)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Pursuit of Happiness: Being Happy, Being Human," 1975 January-February (Box-folder 027:012)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Situation Ethics: Law and Watergate," 1975 Spring (Box-folder 027:013)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Dead or Alive: a Definition," 1975 June (Box-folder 027:014)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Pragmatists and Doctrinaires," 1975 June (Box-folder 027:015)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Famine and Global Policy: an Interview with Joseph Fletcher," by George R. Lucas, Jr. 1975 September 3 (Box-folder 027:016)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethical Considerations in Biomedical Research Involving Human Beings," 1976 March 2-5 (Box-folder 027:017)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Feeding the Hungry: an Ethical Appraisal," 1976 Spring (Box-folder 027:018)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "In Verteidigung des Suizids," 1976, 2 Items (Box-folder 027:019)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "How Do We Go About Making Moral Decisions?" with transcript of discussion, 1978 January 12-14 (Box-folder 027:020)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethics and Recombinant DNS Research," 1978 September (Box-folder 027:021)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Symposium: Clinical Pastoral Education," 1979 April (Box-folder 027:022)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "An Odyssey: from Theology to Humanism," 1979 (Box-folder 027:023)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Hard Choices," with ethics case studies by Joseph Fletcher, 1980 (Box-folder 027:024)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Knowledge, Risk, and the Right to Reproduce: a Limiting Principle," 1980 (Box-folder 027:025)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Daniel Bell's Religions Revival," with enclosed note, unidentified, 1981 Autumn (Box-folder 027:026)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Genetic Control: a Position Paper" [incomplete], 1981 (Box-folder 027:027)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Secular Humanism: It's the Adjective that Counts," 1983 Autumn (Box-folder 027:028)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethics, Politica, and Human Reproduction," with Thomas H. Hunter 1985 Autumn (Box-folder 027:029)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Geriatric Psychiatry: the Case of the MI, DNR, ECT, NG, and DOD," 1986 July (Box-folder 027:030)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "A Humanist Confession," with attached note by [Fletcher] and a draft, [1986], 3 Items (Box-folder 027:031)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Humanism and Theism in Biomedical Ethics," 1987 (Box-folder 027:032)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Courts and Euthanasia," 1987-1988 Winter (Box-folder 027:033)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "On Truth Telling," 1988 Spring (Box-folder 027:034)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethics and Aging: Should Age be a Guidline for Limiting Medical Treatment?" with Daniel Callahan, 1988 June (Box-folder 027:035)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethics and Old Age," 1988 June (Box-folder 027:036)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "The Moral Limits of Knowledge," 1988 Autumn (Box-folder 027:037)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Genetic Control: a Position Paper," 1989 Autumn (Box-folder 027:038)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Arise and Stand Upon Thy Feet," N.D. (Box-folder 027:039)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Behavior Control: It It Ethical?" N.D. (Box-folder 027:040)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Ethicists Ponder Bio-Engineering," N.D. (Box-folder 027:041)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Malvern Movement: Life and Worship," N.D. (Box-folder 027:042)
- Reprints, Fletcher: "Some Propositions About Managing Terminal Illness as Perceived by a Biomedical Moralist," N.D. (Box-folder 027:043)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1928, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:001)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1936, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:002)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1942, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:003)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1947, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:004)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1948, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:005)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1953, 4 Items (Box-folder 028:006)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1955, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:007)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1958, 3 Items (Box-folder 028:008)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1959, 3 Items (Box-folder 028:009)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1960, 3 Items (Box-folder 028:010)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1961, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:011)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1962, 1 Item (Box-folder 028:012)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1963, 11 Items (Box-folder 028:013)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1964, 11 Items (Box-folder 028:014)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1965, 14 Items (Box-folder 028:015)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1966, 11 Items (Box-folder 028:016)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1967, 13 Items (Box-folder 028:017)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1968, 9 Items (Box-folder 029:001)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1969, 7 Items (Box-folder 029:002)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1970, 2 Items (Box-folder 029:003)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1971, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:004)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1972, 3 Items (Box-folder 029:005)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1973, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:006)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1974, 2 Items (Box-folder 029:007)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1975, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:008)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1979, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:009)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1985, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:010)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1986, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:011)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1987, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:012)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1988, 1 Item (Box-folder 029:013)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1989, 2 Items (Box-folder 029:014)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1990, 9 Items (Box-folder 029:015)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, 1992, 2 Items (Box-folder 029:016)
- Reprints, Miscellaneous, N.D., 9 Items (Box-folder 029:017)
- Reviews: Review of Morals and Medicine, [1955 Spring] (Box-folder 030:001)